welcome back everyone
today as usual
we are going to do some small upgrades at out base
but let's follow the instructions this time
we have to get ready for emotional trauma
to do so, I think we should start by gathering even more minerals
don't worry, this time we are using void miners which do not run out
they keep mining forever
we also need some mysterious crystals
which can only be obtained by Callisto's rocks
luckily this planet is not a finite geometrical shape
but an infinite land
we now need something overpowered to process all of these ores
let's craft something op
you know what
even if it is overpowered it might not be enough
let's make three more
maybe next time
and here we go
now I think we should get some help for the next tasks
let's start making some nanites to help us
and a couple more ore plants
while nanites will help us with circuits
we also do need something better for making components
I think this component assembly line will be the best choice for our case
however it looks like we lack the resources for completing its structure
fear not
all we have to do is feed some Oganesson to our miners
to multiply the production by a factor of 64
however we are now running low on power again
and thus we shall take a small break
and power up our helium plant
since it makes some power as byproduct
now we do have more power
but we still have to wait for the completion of the tasks we queued early on
so let's use this time for showing God that we are no longer noobs
let's do that by crafting a certificate that will prove it
thanks to the overclock it will be manageable
anyways as I was saying
while we are waiting for our certificate to be forged
we can start building some more ore processing plants
however we were not only running out of ores but also of fluids
anyways to get so many fluids
we need to research a better pump
and to do so
we have to increase the power of our crypto mining farm by adding some GPUs in its computers
after some more tinkering
we have managed to make our farm reach 3900 Yotta flops
so many flops that not even this dream keeps up with it
and we are now at half the process of forging our certificate
while we wait we can complete our Nano Forge
however this is just the tier 1
which seems to be useful only for unlocking the tier 2
now we have found one issue
this place is not fit for such a big multi block
we shall move it in a more appropriate place
and we shall also have a better power system to keep it up and running
now that we can bring it to tier 2
it is time to find out that we have misplaced it
so time to rebuild it again
however, this time let's make a better wrench for the job
and the proceed into using it like savages
now we proceed into rebuilding the whole thing
this time, at the maximum tier since it is not that costly
and this is the finished work
since we have 5 hours left
I think we should start thinking about project assembly
even though we have almost all the materials
this thing requires a lot of assembly line craftings
I think it is a good idea to review our slime setups to make crafting huge amounts of things easier
and here we go
we now have arranged all the research patterns in a database that is shared across our assembly lines
now if we want to be hired by Fixit Incorporated before the next Christsmas
we have to start working on Project Assembly
and also we must be aware of the capacity of our cobblestone storage
we are quite close to completely filling it
we should probably start working on a better storage
but it appears to be a convoluted process
it is now time to fetch our certificate
it looks like the gods did not accept our certificate
that has to be because we did not go through the emotional trauma
we do still lack some of the materials for the trauma
but fear not
we are working on a machine that will fix every issue
while we wait
we can start working on making a better cobblestone storage
we should also check our base every now and then
sometimes the traffic lights get stuck on red forever
now we have to find an appropriate place for this chunky thing
we should probably ask the CEO of Fixit Incorporated for some tips
this place looks good enough
let's take a selfie for Reddit before it gets shut it down
next we shall farm some mobs to increase our level
so that the gods might notice us
we max out the length of our fusion tunnel
and while working on the meds for the trauma
we can't help but notice that we are genuinely going to need to increase our helium plasma plant for the helium
but the issue is rather about the usage than the production though
let's just say I was lazy with the argon setup
while we wait
we can dedicate ourselves to activities
such as making half of the Kevlar line
I have recorded this activity
and it took me 3 days to upload the video without failures
we go retrieve the miner that is collecting Enceladus stone
and move it to a place that has a stone which contains unstable dust
after these brief distractions
we finally can have a proper extraction of Infinity Catalyst
and finally we can start preparing themets for the emotional trauma
and the gods have finally accepted us in their holy land
we have made some progress
here you can see a collection of 54 multi blocks
they are all required to make only one single output
Kevlar
we are going to need it for higher tier Circuit
and most importantly
for our mother spaceship
talking of space
we must not forget about crafting the parts for our space elevator
let's do some of them
we also need to make one compact MK2 reactor
we only need it for researching MK3
it looks like we only lack deep iron for that craft
this could be avoidable by changing some of our patterns
we are still using some old recipes that are now outperformed by the new ones we have unlocked with all of our progression
let's see where all of the trinium is being used
on a second thought
maybe the best solution is just the simplest one
void miners go baa Ra Ra Ra Ra Ra Ra Ra Ra Ra
talking of old stuff
we should really do something about these old HV reactors
let's do some better wiring and pump them a bit
and here we go
now they work a lot faster
while we wait for our other projects
we can do some experiments with DNA and other weird stuff
we have found a cure for some diseases
but that's not our objective
we are mastering the bacteria of our own planet
so that we can move on to the extraterrestrial ones
now we put our new lab produced mutated alien bacteria into a vat
so that we can increase our collection of delicious refreshing beverages
while our artificial yeast is making drinks
and AE2 is crafting a compact fusion reactor
we take a moment to appreciate our newly built space elevator
that thing is so powerful
that it can shoot us way beyond the moon
it can even launch us straight to Pluto
and it also placed ourselves inside a lander
and on a side note
I didn't even plug the power to that thing
I do wonder where it could send us to if I gave it some power
now I do know that after our mineral extraction
Pluto shrunk so much that it's not longer considered as a planet
but it still does have some nests of mutant alien wolf
more than wolves they look like rabbits
look at how it runs away after you punch it twice
our hunt gave us a schematic
that we swiftly scanned for our research purposes
we are planning to make a shuttle
to go build our future mothership
which we will use to conquer the multiverse
while our multiverse domination plan is on the working
let's do some home brewing
we will need something really dank for celebrating such achievement
first we need to brew some alien plants inside our xenoxen to make some raw radox
next we distill it and take out only the most fine part - light radox
then we crack it twice using silver plasma
we distill again the result to finally obtain some radox gas
then we just add some extra plasma in it, shake it
and we obtain the super high class molten radox polymer
don't drink it all at once
now let's make something useful in our Nano Forge
some silver nanites that will speed up our PCB factory
and here you can see how cute they look
we are sharing them between our two PCB factories
we made two factories due to some issues with the cooling
but also because we want this one to better use the materials
to do so we are going to make it work at 50 microns instead of 100
now while we are crafting our first ultimate battery
let's see how this new tier 9 rocket works
I hope the fuel for the tier 8 rocket will be fine
and off we go
as you can see many thing changed but let's go in order
first thing we let ae2 take care of the longest part
making 8 UMV batteries
here you can see it working on the last four
next we shall personally place all the ingredients in the assembly line
to make this moment more memorable
we should have created a pattern for that thing though
this is a very delicate crafting
if anything goes wrong
we could lose one week worth of resources and crafting
next we shall replace our PSS with the newly acquired battery
and here we go
from the infographic you can see that the amount of energy our new storage can hold is higher than we can pronounce
next we are going to finally work on our mothership
while stuff is crafting
we can start doing the math for how powerful our thrusters must be
here you can see our accurate measures of the weight of some blocks
now that all the parts are ready
we can finally launch ourselves into space
next we create a new mothership
and proceed into landing on it
and here's our newly built mothership
now we have to figure out how to use it
but first we should add some engines
we are using the cooler ones
not because they are faster
but because they do not require us to make a facility for the naquadah fuel
these run on power
the electric power requirement is incredibly low
but it looks like they also need some liquid
so we shall get some xenon
luckily ae2 can reach us even up there
however this is not xenon
and we have to go back in our base to get some of it
while here
we refill our oxygen and fuel tanks
next we do some extra xenon production using some UU matter
we take the little drops that our distillery extracted from air
and fly to our mother ship
hopefully our space elevator which can reach Pluto can also reach our mother ship
or maybe not
we then proceed into building our launch pad over a solid spot
you can see how solid it is by the way it refract the exhausts of our rocket
and here we are
now while the engines are refuelling
I think it's a good time to customize our mothership
we shall have a proper icon for it like this one
now after spending a lot of time searching for our target planet
we realize that we lack of fuel
and our engines can't even hold so much
I think the best idea is to trim the unneeded mass of our ship
however it looks like this didn't work
let's try to first reach a midway spot
and then go to the destination from there
we are now moving
as you can see from the stars almost hitting us
and here you can see our engines throwing away our precious xenon
now that we have arrived
we can notice that the distance is now longer
so we go back to earth
while our new engines are crafting
we shall find a better and faster way to reach our mothership
this rocket is kinda lame
so let's just put our personal world linker on our mothership
so that we can say that we have relocated our base in a compressed space on our mothership
and I think this is a good moment for crafting a Plan B to get back to earth
now that our relocator is ready
we only have to set it up
now that we have increased our propulsion power
we can finally travel to other stars
however it looks like we lack a little bit of energy for going straight to the destination
our engine would need to be able to carry around 1000 more EU
I wish we had a battery capable of holding an unspeakable amount of power
but that is not a big deal
we can still reach the Ra star
this is a long journey
we could stay here watching all the star almost colliding with us
but I think we should be more productive
so let's go into our pocket dimension
don't worry too much about or lack of power
with the new materials
we are going to improve our power production
anyways while we are waiting
we can start working forward to the next tier of circuits
the optical series
these circuits are going to need a lot of components and processing
for now let's start with procuring some purified water
apparently our distilled water is not pure enough
so first we are going to sift the bigger impurities out of some vanilla water
next we are going to heat it a bit
then we run it through a distillation tower
we use a laser to shoot some bacteria out of it
we filter it with some zeolite in a chemical reactor
we shoot it again with a laser
this time using the meme lens
one more run in a distillation tower
and finally we make some nanites have a bath in it
to take out some unknown quantum particles
and this is the complete setup we just described
anyways we have now arrived
and it's time to land on these new planets
the first one is pretty boring
and only has some magnetic mineral
the second one has the best bounties
which you can now see on the screen
and it had some cool dungeons
however the most dangerous planet was
without doubt the third one
at first it looked specific with nice animals
but we had to hide our void miner for its own safety
while the miners are working
we must also check what kind of sick job a new helper is doing
and it appears that he is working on making lag
and a lot of visual glitches
now that we have enough resources
we can start crafting some proper turbines
and we proceed into making them to good use
now it may looks like our power issues are fixed
but it is not
all we did was moving the issue from the battery to our americium plasma tank
欢迎回来，各位
今天照常
我们要给基地做些小升级
但这次咱们按指引来
我们得准备好经历心理创伤了
为此，我觉得该先采集更多矿物
别担心，这次我们用虚空矿机，资源永不枯竭
它们能永远挖下去
还需要些神秘水晶
只能从木卫四的岩石获取
幸好这颗星球并非有限几何体
而是无限大陆
我们现在需要超强设备处理这些矿石
来制作个超模的机器
要知道
就算它性能超模也可能不够用
再做三台
或许下次吧
做好哩
接下来的任务需要些帮手
让我们造些纳米蜂群来辅助我们
再加几个矿石处理厂
纳米蜂群能协助电路生产
但部件制造需要更好方案
这条部件装配线最适合当前需求
但我们似乎缺少完成结构的资源
别慌
只需给矿机加一点鿫
就能让产量提升64倍
但电力又开始告急
所以我们得稍作休整
然后启动氦等离子体产线
因为它能发一些电作为副产
现在电力充裕了
但还需等待早期排队的任务完成
我们趁此机会向神明证明
我们早已不是菜鸟
造个凭证来验证
幸亏能超频，制作时间才变得可接受
总之，如我所说
等待凭证锻造时
我们可以再建些矿石处理厂
然而不仅矿石见底，流体也不够了
要获取大量流体
需研发更好的泵
为此
得给矿机加装GPU提升算力
稍作调试后
矿场算力已达每秒3.9e27次浮点运算
算力高到连梦境都跟不上
现在凭证锻造过半
等待期间，我们去完成纳米锻炉
但这只是初阶版本
似乎仅用于解锁二阶
现在我们发现了一个问题
这区域不适合大型多方块结构
得移到更合适的位置
我们还需要更好的电网维持它的运行
我们现在能把纳米锻炉升级到二阶了
却发现摆放位置有误
只能重建
这次我们造把更好的扳手
然后像野蛮人一样猛用
现在我们重建整个结构
直接造最高阶，因为成本并不高
这是完工成果
既然我们还剩5小时
我们该考虑“组装计划”了
虽然我们材料基本齐全
但这需要大量装配线合成
让我们重构一下以前的龟速产线，简化大批量合成
就像这样
我们现在将所有研究蓝图存入装配线共享数据库
如果想在下次圣诞节前被菲克斯公司录用
必须开始“组装计划”
还得注意圆石存储容量
它快溢出了
我们该建个更好的存储系统
但过程似乎很复杂
现在是时候取回凭证
看来神明未认可我们的凭证
这一定是因为我们还没遭受心理创伤
我们还缺些导致创伤的材料
别担心
我们正在造能解决所有问题的机器
在等待期间
我们先升级圆石存储系统
还需定期检查基地
有时信号灯会卡在红灯
我们得找个合适位置放这大家伙
或许该咨询菲克斯公司CEO的建议
这位置不错
在它关闭前拍张自拍发Reddit
接下来是刷怪升级
以便让神明注意到我们
我们将聚变隧道长度拉满
在我们制造心理创伤所需要的药时
我们发现需要扩建氦等离子体工厂
来获取更多氦气
但问题在于消耗而非生产
都怪我当初氩气配置太敷衍
在等待的同时
我们可以专注于类似于
"完成一半凯夫拉产线"的活动
我录下了这个过程
花了3天才成功上传视频
我们取回采集土卫二岩石的矿机
转移到含有不稳定粉尘的地方
在经过了这些琐事后
我们终于能正常提取无限催化剂
可以开始准备治疗心理创伤所需的药剂了
神明终于接纳我们进入圣地
我们已有了一些进展
这是有54个多方块结构的产线
一切只为产出一种物品
凯夫拉
高阶电路需要它
更重要的是
我们的母舰也需要它
说到太空
别忘了制造太空电梯部件
让我们先造一部分
我们还需要紧凑型MK2聚变堆
它仅用于研究MK3
我们似乎只缺深铁矿
调整合成配方可避免此需求
我们还在用旧配方，而新解锁的配方效率更高
让我看看三元金属都用在哪了
转念一想
或许简单方案最有效
只需要虚空矿机这样这样再那样那样
说到旧设备
我们该处理这些老旧的HV大化反了
让我们优化线路并升压
这样就好了
现在效率高多了
我们在等待其他项目时
可以做些关于DNA和其他奇怪东西的实验
发现了某些疾病疗法
但那并非我们的目标
我们正在掌握本星球细菌特性
以便研究外星细菌
将实验室培养的变异外星细菌放入培养罐
用来增加我们的酿造特饮收藏
在我们的人造酵母正酿酒的同时
AE正在合成紧凑聚变堆
我们趁机欣赏新建的太空电梯
这设备威力强大
能将我们送至月球之外
甚至直达冥王星
还自动将我们装入登陆舱
顺便说一句
我都没给太空电梯通电
很好奇供电后它能把我们传送到哪
我现在明白了，在我们进行矿物开采后
冥王星萎缩到不再是行星
但它仍有变异外星狼巢穴
这家伙更像兔子而非狼
看它挨两拳就跑的样子
这场狩猎给予我们一张图纸
我们迅速扫描了它用于研究
我们计划建造穿梭机
用来建造未来的母舰
再用这母舰征服多元宇宙
在多元宇宙征服计划进行时
让我们来点私酿
我们需要顶级佳酿庆祝如此成就
先把外星植物浸泡在异氙中
制造出粗制拉多X
然后将其蒸馏，只提取最轻的超轻拉多X
然后用银等离子体裂解两次
再次蒸馏得到拉多X气
加入额外等离子体震荡混合
制成超高级材料：熔融拉多X聚合物
温馨提示：美酒虽好，可不要贪杯哦
现在用纳米锻炉造些实用物品
一些银纳米蜂群来加速PCB工厂
看它们多可爱
两个PCB工厂共用这些蜂群
建两个工厂是因散热问题
也为了更好利用材料
让这个工厂以50微米而非100微米精度运行
在我们合成出首个终极电池时
让我们测试一下新九阶火箭的性能
希望八阶火箭燃料能用
出发
如你所见变化很大，让我们按顺序说明
我们先让AE处理最耗时部分
制造8个UMV电池
现在在合成最后四个
我们接着亲手将原料放入装配线
为了让这时刻更难忘
我们其实应该给这配方写样板
这是相当精密的合成
若有闪失
将损失一周资源与心血
接下来用新电池替换原有的能源站
搞定
信息面板显示的新电池的容量超乎想象
接下来，我们总算开始建造母舰
在其他东西合成时
我们计算推进器所需功率
这是部分方块的精确重量测量
现在所有部件就绪
我们终于能飞向太空
接下来我们创建母舰
并登陆
这就是我们新建成的母舰
我们现在要研究怎么操作它
我们要先安装引擎
选更酷的型号
并非因为他们产生的速度更快
而是无需使用需要新产线提取的硅岩燃料
这些引擎靠电力运行
而他们的电力需求极低
但似乎还需某种液体
我们去拿一些氙气
幸好AE能无线连接到这里
但这不是氙气
我们得回基地取
在基地时
我们顺便补充氧气和燃料罐
用UU物质增产氙气
收集蒸馏塔提取的空气微量成分
然后飞回母舰
希望能直达冥王星的太空电梯也能到母舰
呃好像不太行
我们在坚实的的地方建造发射台
看火箭尾焰折射的样子就知道多坚实
堂堂抵达
引擎补充燃料时
该自定义母舰标识了
用这样的专属图标
经过长时间的搜寻目标行星后
我们发现燃料不足
我们的引擎甚至装不了那么多燃料
最好削减母舰的多余质量
但这似乎无效
我们先尝试抵达中途点
再从那里前往目的地
员工正在快速移动
以至于星星几乎要撞上我们
你可以看到引擎喷出的宝贵氙气
抵达后发现
我们距离目的地更远了
所以我们返回地球
在新引擎制造的同时
我们寻找更快抵达母舰的方法
这火箭有点拉
所以我们在母舰放下私人维度传送门
等价于我们将基地迁至母舰上的压缩空间里
这是我们准备返回地球的备用方案的好时机
传送器就绪
我们只需要配置好它
推进功率提升后
我们终于能前往其他恒星了
但我们缺少一些直达目的地所需的能源
引擎还需多存约1000EU能量
真希望有个容量惊人的电池
问题不大
我们仍能抵达Ra恒星
这是漫长的旅程
我们可以在此观看擦肩星光
但我们应更高效利用时间
于是我们进入私人维度
不必担心能源短缺
有了新材料
我们能提升发电效率
在等待时
我们可研究下一阶电路
光学系列
这些电路需要大量组件与加工
我们先准备纯净水
蒸馏水纯度显然不够
我们先筛除原版水中的大颗粒杂质
适当加热
通过蒸馏塔处理
激光消灭细菌
沸石化学过滤
再次激光照射
透过这个玩梗的透镜
二次蒸馏处理
纳米蜂群浸取以去除量子微粒
这是刚才描述的产线的样子
无论如何，我们已抵达
是时候登陆新行星了
第一颗很无趣
仅有磁性矿物
第二颗资源丰富
如图可见
它还有酷炫地牢
但最危险的无疑是第三颗
乍一看，它风景宜人动物友善
但我们不得不隐藏虚空矿机以保安全
当矿机工作时
我们必须检查新助手在做什么变态事情
他似乎在制造卡顿
以及大量视觉bug
现在我们有了充足的资源
我们开始制造合理配置的涡轮机
并投入使用
电力问题看似解决
其实不然
我们只是将问题从电池转移到镅等离子体储罐
（OP同时是矿物处理(Ore Process)和超模(OverPowered)的简称）
蓝色染料→